Westwood-Holmby Historical Society records, 1907-2014
UCLA Library Special Collections
Westwood-Holmby Historical Society records
Bulk, 1989-2003
1907-2014
2253
UCLA Library Special Collections
25.2 linear ft. (15 boxes, 12 oversized flat boxes, 5 flat boxes, 1 shoe box, 1 poster tube, 1 oversize panorama enclosure)
The collection is comprised of administrative, organizational and membership files of the Westwood-Holmby Historical Society as well as materials about Los Angeles gathered between 1989 and 2014 through the Research Committee of the WHHS. Historical research and community support were the main objectives of WHHS.
Conditions Governing Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance through out electronic paging system using the "Request items" button.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7834512
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Westwood-Holmby Historical Society, 2014.
Biography/History
The Westwood-Holmby Historical Society (1989 – 2014) was a non-profit public benefit organization founded as an outgrowth of Westwood’s 60th Anniversary celebration. WHHS was a volunteer led and run organization dedicated to the research and documentation of people, places and events of historical significance in Westwood-Holmby, a neighborhood in west Los Angeles, California. They were active in building their own archives of photographs, newspaper clippings and oral histories among other records that were both collected and created by the WHHS. Lectures, exhibitions and tours were often curated by WHHS for the community as well as for local schools. Organizational priorities included petitioning for cultural heritage sites and being vocal in the bureaucratic measures that determine historical status in Los Angeles.
Scope and Content
In this collection are the administrative and research materials pertaining to the Westwood-Holmby Historical Society. Administrative files include bylaws, meeting minutes and various correspondence records. Files relating to specific events that WHHS programmed are also included in this collection and contain flyers, posters and photographs about and documenting their events and lectures. Membership files like member lists and guestbooks can also be found in this collection. WHHS’s most active unit was their research committee, who gathered the bulk of the content of this collection between 1989 and 2014. Their research materials include subseries collections that were donated to WHHS: the Rowe Radar Baldwin papers, the Robert and Blanche Campbell papers, and the George Gregson papers. These donated collections revolve around the lives of their donors and their relationship to the Westwood neighborhood. Research committee materials include a large amount of photographs, ephemera, publications and information about the family who developed the neighborhood of Westwood, the Janss family.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Administrative, 1989 - 2014
Series 2: Events, 1989 - 2003
Series 3: Membership, 1989 - 2003
Series 4: Historical Research, 1907 - 2014
Subseries 4.1: Rowe Radar Baldwin papers, 1929-1992
Subseries 4.2: Robert and Blanche Campbell papers, 1930-1990
Subseries 4.3: George Gregson Westwood Real Estate papers, 1929-2014
Subseries 4.4: Research Committee, 1907-2010
Subseries 4.5: Oral Histories, 1989-2000
Westwood-Holmby Historical Society--Archives.
Container List
- Administrative., 1989 - 2014.
  Scope and Content
  This first series in the collection focuses on the administrative and legal files of the Westwood-Holmby Historical Society. Articles of incorporation, tax status and by laws accompany organizational level materials like meeting minutes, logo designs and correspondence.
  Organization and Arrangement
  Files at this level are arranged alphabetically.
  - Articles of Incorporation., 1989 - 1991. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, Pamphlets and Press Releases., 1989 - 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - By Laws., 1992. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: From Westwood-Holmby Historical Society., 1990 - 2008. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Samples., 1992 - 1997. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: To Westwood-Holmby Historical Society., 1990 - 1992. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dissolution., 2014. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Historical Committee., 1989. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation Overlay Zones., 1991. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Logo Design and Information., 1989 - 1990. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Minutes., 1989 - 1992. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes., 1993. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Operational Notes., 1991. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Tax Exemption., 1989 - 1990. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Historical Society Posters., undated. (Box 30)
    Contains three posters, two copies of an original design promoting Westwood, and the third a poster of the University of California.
- Events., 1989 - 2003.
  The documents in this series represent programmed events and lectures developed by WHHS. The bulk of the series contains photographs, flyers and press releases pertaining to the Celebrate Westwood 60th Committee of which the WHHS was created out of. Other events documented in this series include historical walking tours and guest lectures on historical architectural monuments all within the neighborhood of Westwood.
  Files at this level are arranged chronologically.
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Committee Transition., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Community Research., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Correspondence., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Documentation., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Event Schedules., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Event, Committee Kickoff., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Event, Janss Day., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Event, Do-It-Yourself Walking Tour., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Event, UCLA Homecoming Parade., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Meetings., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press, magazine - LA West., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press, magazine - LA West supplement., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press, magazine - UCLA Magazine., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press, newspaper - LA Business Council supplement., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press, newspaper - clippings., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press - other., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Press Releases., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Supplements., 1989. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Westwood 60th Anniversary: Display images., 1989. (Box 17)
  - Westwood Village Art Shows., 1990. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Open House., June 1991. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fox Studio Walking Tour., October 6, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Red Car Days., March 29, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bob Pierson Lecture., April 27, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles Conservancy - Union Station Event., October 1993. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Holiday Party., December 14, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Leslie Heumann Lecture - Researching Your House., April 24, 1995. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Karen Hudson Lecture on Architecture of Paul R Williams., November 7, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rancho to Communities: 75 Years., November 17, 1997. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Autumn Reception., November 16, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jim Heimann Lecture - Westwood Then and Now., May 15, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Janice Marscher Lecture., April 28, 2003. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Event Flyers Collection., 1992 - 2003. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Trivia., undated. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Slide Presentation Notes., undated. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - UCLA-Westwood Photography Sale., undated. (Box 29)
    This item is mounted on foam board.
- Membership., 1989 - 2003.
  These files document a few key members of the WHHS, Wendy Kaplan and Greg Fischer. Fischer was on the board of directors for the WHHS as well as a historical walking tour guide of Los Angeles and an advocate for the restoration of historical Los Angeles neighborhood titles. Kaplan was the Founding President of the WHHS until her retirement in 1991. Also in this collection are photographs from member only meetings and lists of members throughout the years in the form of guestbooks and lists.
  Files at this level are arranged by subject.
  - Guestbook., 1989 - 1991. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Guestbook., 1997 - 2003. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Member: Greg Fischer., 1992 - 1995. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Member: Wendy Kaplan., December 1991. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Contains 35mm negatives.
  - Member Only Meetings., 1989 - 1992. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Membership and Attendance., 1989 - 2003. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Historical Research., 1907 - 2014.
  The fourth series in this collection contains the bulk of the materials. The Research Committee within the WHHS was the most active sector of the society due to their mission to preserve and restore historically significant information and architecture relating to Westwood and surrounding neighborhoods in Los Angeles. This series is comprised of five subseries, three of which are small donated collections by people or families who had affluent and honored standing in the Westwood community. Subjects that make appearances in this series are the prominent Westwood families of Janss and Burbank and Los Angeles city planning materials. The city planning materials include tract home maps and advertisements as well as correspondence on infrastructure and architectural developments. The last subseries in this series includes oral histories recorded on cassette and mini cassette as well as transcriptions of those interviews in bound book form.
  Files at this level are arranged chronologically unless otherwise stated.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  SERIES CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
  - Rowe Radar Baldwin papers., 1929 - 1992.
    Rowe Radar Baldwin was a 1929 UCLA alum. From 1934 to 1938 she wrote a column called for the Westwood Hills Press as part of her duties as Publicity Director of the Janss Investment Corporation, for whom she worked from 1929 to 1938. She began writing in June 1934 and resigned in April 1938, replaced by Gertrude Harlan. Following, Baldwin worked as UCLA’s athletic ticket manager from 1943 to 1973. She was a founding member of the UCLA Gold Shield. Baldwin assisted Westwood-Holmby Historical Society in research for exhibitions and events. In 1975 and 1976, Baldwin assisted Donald Combs in research for exhibit at Contempo Westwood Center. In 1989, Baldwin assisted in the Westwood 60th Anniversary by providing valuable insight and details about the town. Baldwin served as Honorary Society Director of WHHS from 1989 to 1995. These papers were donated from Baldwin to WHHS in 1992. Her papers includes correspondence with Warner Bros studio, UCLA, San Bernardino School District and other individuals and businesses she helped provide with information or photographs of Westwood during her time as a columnist. Newspaper clipping from her column, as well as about Janss Investment Corporation can be found in this subseries. One folder is dedicated to child actress Jane Withers and her interaction with UCLA and Ms. Radar in 1936.
    - Rowe Radar Baldwin., 1929 - 1989. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Village Raider" column., 1934 - 1992. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Early Janss Demonstration Homes., 1935 - 1937. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Jose de Buenos Aires newspaper clipping., 1936. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence on "Village Raider"., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Jane Withers., 1936 - 1939. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings., 1937 - 1961. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Colorful First Years" Westwood Village article., 1952. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - History of Westwood., 1960s - 1989. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Village Raider" column copies., May 1, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Westwood 60th Anniversary articles., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - "Village Raider" column copies from Baldwin's scrapbook, 1934 - 1938., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - "Village Raider" column copies from Baldwin's scrapbook, 1934 - 1938., 1989. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence with Wendy Kaplan., 1989 - 1991. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Janss Story., 1992. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Note from Rowe., 1992. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Robert and Blanche Campbell papers., 1930 - 1990.
    Robert and Blanche Campbell were business owners in Westwood in the 1930s to 1980s. They owned and operated Campbell’s Bookstore located at 10918 Le Conte Ave. Materials in this subseries include administrative and publicity files associated with Campbell’s Bookstore, community service activities of the Campbells, and photographs of the Campbell family. Also included in this subseries are ephemera about the Westwood Village Lions Club and Westwood Village Studio donated by the daughter of Robert and Blanche, Clarice Campbell and her friend Dorothy Ross, daughter of Ruth and Gene Ross.
    - Campbell's Bookstore stationary., 1930s - 1950s. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Campbell's Bookstore stamps., 1929 - 1954. (Box 16)
    - Campbell columns., 1936 - 1952. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ye Village Tattler newspaper., 1937 - 1981. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Tropical Ice Garden - Clarice Campbell., 1939 - 1990. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Campbell Photographs., 1948 - 1962. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Independence Press Award of Merit, Robert Campbell., May 1962. (Box 17)
    - Campbell and Bretano's newspaper articles., 1962 - 1981. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Community Service., 1963 - 1970. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Eugene Gilbert - Evening Outlook., 1964 - 1985. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - From Dorothy Ross and Clarice Campbell - Westwood Village Lions Club / postcard., 1967 - 1990. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Outstanding Community Service Award, Blanche Campbell., 1970. (Box 16)
    - Outstanding Community Service Award, Robert Campbell., 1972. (Box 16)
    - Community Citizens of the Year Award, Bob and Blanche Campbell., January 21, 1982. (Box 17)
    - Mayor's Certificate of Appreciation, Blanche and Bob Campbell., January 21, 1982. (Box 21)
    - Ruth Ross "Westwood Village Studio" autobiography., 1984. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Oakley's Hair Stylists., 1987 - 1989. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Blanch Campbell portrait., undated. (Box 17)
    - Campbell's Bookstore matches., undated. (Box 16)
    - Robert Campbell signature stamp., undated. (Box 16)
    - Robert Campbell El Ranchero de San Jose de Buenos Aires Identification card., undated. (Box 16)
    - Rotary International Paul Harris Fellow medallion and pin., undated. (Box 16)
  - Geroge Gregson Westwood Real Estate papers., 1929 - 2014.
    George Gregson (Gregovich), 1904 – 1997, was the Vice President for the Janss Investment Corporation. His parents emigrated from Serbia to the United States and raised George in Arizona. Gregson began his career as an appraiser at a mortgage company and worked his way up to executive and then Vice President at the Janss Investment Corporation. After Janss Corp sold the land in Westwood, Gregson continued to own property in Westwood Village, including Linde Medical Plaza land, and various office locations. He was married to Patricia Cluff Janss from January 12th, 1935 until her death in 1939. Included in this subseries are materials related to Mr. Gregson’s time at Janss Investment Corporation, titles and deeds of the sale of Westwood Village, and his personal letter opener.
    - Tract Maps and Deeds., 1929 - 1941. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Janss History Publication,., 1930. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Brothers Property Zone Atlas of Los Angeles County., 1946. (Box 20)
    - Janss Investment Corporation Sears Warehouse Site., 1948 - 1949. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Westwood Hills., 1940s. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Westwood Village Property Sale I., 1951 - 1960. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Westwood Village Property Sale II., 1951 - 1960. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Westwood Village Appraisals., 1953 - 1954. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Fox Hills Realty - Oil and Mineral Rights - Janss., 1954. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Photos: Janss Investment Corporation Properties., 1954. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Westwood Village., 1958 - 1988. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Photos: Peter Caine collection of mounted Westwood photos., circa 1960s. (Box 20)
    - Right of Way Quitclaim., 1960 - 1984. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Janss Westwood Publicity., 1961 - 1992. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Janss Right of Way - Southern Pacific Electric., 1968 - 1971. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, demolition is started., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, start of construction., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, demolished., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, demolition views., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, views., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Photos: Exposition Rd and Wesdtwood Blvd, views and Santa Monica Pier., 1992. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - George Gregson Westwood Real Estate Papers History and Description., 2014. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Maps: Tract and Plans., undated. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Photocopies: 1929 Janss Deed to Adrew and Myron Meyer., undated. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Photocopies: Articles on Geroge Gregson., undated. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Photocopies: Westwood Janss History., undated. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - George Gregson Letter Opener., undated. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Photos: Janss Investment Corporation properties., undated. (Box 17)
    - Maps: Cloth Tract Maps of Westwood area., undated. (Box 29)
  - Research Committee., 1907 - 2010.
    The research committee in the Westwood-Holmby Historical Society was the core of the group's activities and interests. They sought to gain information and insight on their neighborhood in order to protect the rights of and inform landowners as well as register certain sites as historical places. Much of their research ended up contributing to the many exhibitions they had over the years.
    Files at this level are arranged chronologically within subjects.
    - 60th Anniversary: Research., 1989. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Associations: Westwood Hills Business Village., 1922 - 1930. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Associations: G-P Club., 1940. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Associations: Masonic Club and Contempo Center., 1976. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Associations: Other Historical Society By Laws., 1984 - 1989. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Associations: Other Historical Societies., 1988 - 2003. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Associations: Westwood Hills Business Village., 1922 - 1930. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Associations: Westwood Village Association., 1991 - 1993. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Associations: Westwood Community Council., 2010. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Associations: Los Rancheros de San Jose de Buenos Aires Club., undated. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Associations: Los Rancheros de San Jose de Buenos Aires gavel., undated. (Box 26)
    - Business: Hamner and Son photographs., circa 1925. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Business: Hamner and Son photographs., circa 1925 - 1930s. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Business: Religious., circa 1940s - 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Business: Directories., 1950 - 2001. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Business: Hamner and Son ephemera., 1951 - 1959. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Business: Glendale Federal Savings., undated. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Business: Hamner and Son photobook., undated. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Business: Hamner and Son, John Morgan Hamner portrait., undated. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Business: Potter's Hardware deck of cards., undated. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Business: Westwood business cards., undated. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence., 1992 - 2014. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Development: Westwood master plan newspaper clippings., 1958 - 1963. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Development: Traffic congestion plan., 1958 - 1971. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Development: Historical and Cultural resources survey - survey guide., 1981. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Development: Cultural Resource Documentation Report: Westwood Village., 1985. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Development: Improvement Plans., 1985 - 1992. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Development: Westwood Village Specific Plan., 1986 - 1987. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Development: Cultural Resource Documentation Report: Westwood, North and East Villages., 1987. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Development: Cultural Resource Documentation Report: Westwood, North and East Villages., 1987. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Development: The West Los Angeles Subregional Planning Area., 1990. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Development: Los Feliz Improvement Association., 1991. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Development: Westwood Village Management., 1992 - 1993. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Development: SMEDRA / Save Westwood Village., 1998 - 2002. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Development: Privilege Parking., circa 1990s. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Development: Nansay Incorporated., undated. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Development: Notated photocopies of development ads., undated. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Development: Faculty units - University Crest - Old streets of Monterey., undated. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Development: Apartment center - Village - North Village., undated. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Development: University Entrance Park., undated. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Development: Holmby Hills., undated. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Development: Fox Hills - Country Club Units., undated. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Development: Prosperity Units., undated. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Development: Los Angeles County Index Map and Zoning., undated. (Box 29)
    - Development: Santa Monica Index Map and Zoning., undated. (Box 29)
    - Ephemera: Security Federal Savings Westwood Village, 25 year brochure., 1969. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ephemera: "Yesterday Tripping" Los Angeles History., 1984. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Ephemera: Billy Bengston poster., 1989. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Ephemera: Westwood Village postcards., 1989 - 1990. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ephemera: Westwood Park illustration., undated. (Box 32)
    - Janss: Scrapbook, Investment Corporation., 1911 - 1964. (Box 22)
    - Janss: Family and friends photographs and family tree., circa 1930s. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Janss: Business yearbook., 1935. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Janss: Mabel Jellison-Burbank., 1935 - 1989. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Janss: Sales Department Tracts of Westwood Hills., 1936 - 1937. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Janss: Christmas Tribute to Emma Janss., 1940. (Box 31)
    - Janss: Scrapbook., circa 1950s - 1960s. (Box 23)
      General note
      This item is fragile.
    - Janss: Janss Investment Corporation in UCLA Monthly., 1979. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Janss: Parkinson Spirit of Urbanism Award., 1995. (Box 10, Folder 19)